Nyam nyam nyam nyam...
（朱莉）
ニャムニャム　ニャムニャム…
（琴音）おかしい…　ヘン
No good.
Too strange.
あッ　どうしたの？
What's wrong?
Senpai hasn't done anything for so long...
先輩が　さっきから
ずっと動かないの
inside the post office.
郵便局の中で
…て　ＧＰＳ！？
A GPS?!
あのね～　琴音ちゃん
盗聴と電子的ストーキング行為は
Listen, Kotone-chan,
you have to be twenty-one before you can wiretap or be a stalker!
二十歳になってから
じッ　地蔵様が…
Th-The statue is...
≪（琴音）先輩？
Senpai?
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru...
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari de
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai!
might prove to be a big opportunity!
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo mukeru yo
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyanderful
It's really a wonderful cat power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 12!
Can Heaven Wait?
（楓）何だったんだろう　アレ
I wonder what that was about.
Well, I hope this will lift the curse a bit.
《（潤平）これで少しは
ユルくなってくれっかな　呪い》
I see the shadow of a black cat behind you.
《≪（朱莉）後ろに
黒い猫の影が見える》
Were you cursed by the cat statue?
《猫地蔵にでも呪われた？》
高坂くん…
Kousaka-kun...
（住職）ピザは　うまいの～
I love pizza.
おッ　お前達は　もう食わんのか
You're done already?
後ほど　夜食として
家で　いただきます
We'll have them as a late-night snack at home.
ほう　ダイエットは
もう　ええんかい
You're not dieting anymore?
Victory!
ビクトリー！
I-It's none of your business!
いッ　いいでしょう　別に
たまには　おなかが
すくときだってあるの
We get hungry sometimes too.
Let's go, Kotone-chan.
行こう　琴音ちゃん
うん
Yeah.
ワシ　寂しッ
I'm so lonely.
（ニャムサス）う～ん
（タマ）ニャンニャン　ニャンニャン…
（ノワール）う～ん…　ニャ？
（タマ）ニャンニャ～ン
しッ！
Senpai, dinner time.
先輩や～　ご飯ですよ～
ほら　お食べ　エヘヘヘ
Here, eat up.
ううッ
すっかりノラ扱い　情けない
I'm being treated like a stray cat.
It's pathetic!
Stop complaining!
ぜいたく言わないの　こうして
かくまってあげてんだから
At least we're caring for you.
Wh-What'd you do that for?!
何すんだよ　コラッ
Give it back!
This is bad.
ダメね　お札で何とか
呪いの進行を食い止めてるけど
We're using talismans to control the curse...
...but the ears come back as soon as you take off that hat.
帽子を脱ぐと　すぐにまた
ネコ耳が生えてきてしまいます
Sorry for causing both of you so much trouble.
スマン　２人とも　迷惑かけて
まったくよ
Seriously!
I have an express message to send...
《速達いっちょう　衛星フォボスまで》
to the moon Phobos.
《（局員Ａ）はッ　はい？》
Wh-What?
I must tell Great King Nyangoros about the impending crisis on Earth.
《かの地　ニャンゴルモア大王様に》
《地球の危機を
お伝えせねばならぬのＤｅａｔｈ》
Oh, and make it COD if possible.
《できれば着払いで》
《（局員Ａ）あの…》
Um...
Psychic!
《（Ｂ）デンパだ》
《（Ｃ）デンパの人だ》
She's the psychic type.
Junpei-kun is taking so long.
《（千鶴）潤平くん　遅いなあ》
I'll eat his then.
《よ～し　食べちゃえ》
《ああ～》
《しばし！》
All right.
《あッ　ここーッ？》
In here?!
《あッ！》
《（せきこむ）》
I'm done for...
《もう　ダメ…》
Hey... Senpai!
《ちょッ　先輩！》
《あッ　大丈夫？》
Y-You okay?!
何とか　こっそり連れ出したけど
I was able to sneak you out, but...
What should we do now?
この先　どうしていいやら
フフッ
先輩　一生　飼い殺してあげますね
Senpai, I'll take care of you until death.
はい　これ　婚約首輪です
Here, this is an engagement collar.
はあ
（朱莉）…て　イチャつくな～→
Stop flirting!
ヒトが
マジメに考えてあげてるのに！
I'm trying to think seriously here!
大体　何で急に
こんなことに　なったわけ？
Anyway, why is this happening so suddenly?!
Don't you have any clue?!
心当たりは　ないの？
B-But still...
そッ　そう言われても
It's from Sumiyoshi.
住吉だ
Hello?
もしもし？
[TEL]（加奈子）よう　高バカ
Hey, Koubaka!
I heard that you'd been cursed.
[TEL]オメエ　呪われてんだって？
[TEL]ニャハハハ
なッ！？
あッ　カナちゃん
Kana-chan!
Kaede is worried about you, so she came to talk to me.
（加奈子）何か　楓が心配しててさあ
アタシに相談してきたんだけど
Y-Yeah?
[TEL]そッ　そっか
ちょっと来いよ
Come on over.
アタシら　今
１丁目のファミにいんだけど
We're in the family restaurant in 1-chome.
Sorry, maybe some other time!
[TEL]悪い　また今度！
何だよ　チッ
What?!
Sheesh.
Why bother worrying?
ほっとけば？
呪いなんて　あるわけねえじゃん
There's no such thing as a curse.
どうせまた　何か勝手に
ヘマこいてんだろ　アイツ
I'm sure he's just being a klutz again.
Y-Yeah...
うッ　うん
でも　高坂くんには
But I cause trouble for Kousaka-kun all the time.
いろいろ迷惑かけちゃってるし
You think so?
そっか？　どっちかっつーと
It's more like he causes trouble for you.
アイツが　お前に
迷惑かけてる気が…
That's not true!
そんなことないよ
私　高坂くんには　いっつも…
Kousaka-kun always...
Always what?
いっつも？
あ…
I always appreciate what he does,
いつも感謝してるし
and I hope I can be friends with him.
仲よくできたらいいなって
思ってる
そう思ってると思うよ　アイツも
I'm sure he thinks so too.
Why don't you talk to him?
何なら　じかで話してみれば？
２人で　いい機会だし
Now would be a good time to do it.
But...
でも
あッ　赤くなった
You're blushing.
あッ　誤解しないでね
私は　あくまで友達として
P-Please don't take this the wrong way.
I just want to be friends—
Yeah, yeah.
すいませ～ん
（ウエートレス）は～い
Excuse me!
Coming.
この　マーベラストロベリー白玉ほうじ茶パフェ
１つ　くださ～い
I'll take this Marvelous Strawberry Green Tea Parfait.
Right away.
（ウエートレス）かしこまりました
I'm gonna visit the bathroom.
んじゃ　ちょっくら
トイレ　行ってくるわ
チェッ
余計なこと言っちまったかなあ
Maybe that was a little overboard.
けど…
But...
うん　これでいいんだよ　きっと
I'm sure everything will be okay.
≪（朱莉）そっか　なるほどね～
I see.
The Mizuno girl learned about the curse.
あの水野って人が　呪いのことを…
Yeah.
何でか知らんが
どうやら疑ってるらしい
I don't know how it happened, but I guess she suspects.
We'd better do something before it's too late.
手を打たないと　ヤバイわよ
このままじゃ
先輩の呪いも　ヒドくなるし
If we leave things the way they are,
your curse will get worse,
あの人も　不幸に巻き込んじゃう
and she'll be engulfed in misfortune too.
That's wonderful too.
それは　それで…
Kotone-chan, control your misfortune fetish for right now.
琴音ちゃん
不幸萌えは　今はカンベンしてね
But how do we clear up Mizuno's misunderstanding?
けど　水野の疑いを解く方法かあ
一体　どうすりゃ…
What can we do?
ひらめいたよ
I have an idea!
Lend me your ears.
（ニャムサス）アンタ達　耳をお貸し
（ノワール・タマ）ニャムねえさん
Nyam Nee-san?
What?
何　どうかしたの？
What's going on?
いや
何か　いい案を思いついたらしい
Apparently she came up with a plan.
うん？　全然　わかんない
I don't understand at all.
〈気になんないのかな〉
Doesn't it bother her?
〈カナちゃん　高坂くんのこと
きっと好きなはずなのに〉
I'm sure that Kana-chan has feelings for Kousaka-kun.
《何なら　じかで話してみれば？》
Why don't you talk to him?
《２人で　いい機会だし》
Now would be a good time to do it.
Wh-Why is my heart racing so fast?
なッ　何で
こんなにドキドキするんだろう
Whenever I think about Kousaka-kun...
高坂くんのこと考えると…
I don't know this number.
知らない番号
はい　どちら様ですか？
Yes, who is this?
[TEL]ああ　水野？
こッ　高坂だけど～
Mizuno?
Th-This is Kousaka.
Wh-What's going on?
[TEL]どッ　どうしたの？
ばッ　番号　交換してたっけ
D-Did we exchange numbers?
Yeah? Uh, well, you know...
うッ　うん…　まあ　アハハハ
ウフフフ　先輩の周辺情報は
すべて把握済み
I have all the data about Senpai and his environment.
（タマ）しっかし
ヘタクソな芝居ですねい　ダンナ
Anyway, he sucks at acting.
しッ
黙って見てな
Shut up and watch.
Well, uh, could you, like, spare some time tomorrow?
その　悪いけど　明日ちょっと
つきあっていただけますだろうか
[TEL]えッ？
相談したいことがあるんでね
There's something I want to talk to you about.
折り入って　うん
こんなこと　水野にしか…
You're the only person I can ask.
[TEL]はッ　はい　私でよければ
S-Sure! If I'll do.
Yeah.
うん　うん　わかった
Yeah, okay.
どど…　どうしよう！
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What should I do?!
ねえ　何だと思う？　テツヤさん
マサキさん　ヒロシさん！
What do you think this is about,
Tetsuya-san, Masaki-san, Hiroshi-san?!
Yeah, I need to...
そうだよね　丁半…
いや　白黒つけないと
I need to settle this for good.
うんッ
私　頑張る　頑張るよ！
I'll do it!
I'll really do it!
That's the spirit, onee-chan!
Thank you, guys.
ありがとう　みんな
常盤の月も　今宵かぎり
The moon above Tokiwa is watching us too.
I, the young woman Mizuno Kaede, will go and do it!
女一匹　水野楓
いかせていただきますッ
遅いなあ　高坂くん
He's late.
水野ーッ
Mizuno!
悪い　待たせた～
Sorry I'm late.
あッ　あの　話って！？
U-Um, so you need to talk to me?
Yeah, I think I've been cursed.
いや～　実は俺
呪われちゃったみたいでさあ
Kousaka
くわばら　くわばら…
Please... please...
いやね　こないだ　バイト仲間に
罰ゲームで名前　書かされちゃって
My coworkers made me write my name here after losing a game.
それから　妙に不幸続きで
こりゃ　マジで呪われてんのかと
I've been plagued with bad luck ever since,
so I think I've been cursed.
くわばら　くわばら～
Please... please...
But I can't talk about this with Sumiyoshi or Haruhiko.
でも　住吉や晴彦達には
相談できねえし
バカにされそうじゃん？　だから
They might make fun of me, you know.
So...
≪（朱莉）あッ
うわッ
も～う　まさか落書きしたの？
Geez!
You defaced it?!
このバチ当たり！
You blasphemer!
Sorry, sorry.
ああ～　ごめん　ごめん
では　おはらいを
Let's perform the purification.
Cat, cat, cat, cat, welcoming cat,
猫　猫　猫　猫　まねき猫
bring us happiness and keep us from harm.
招福奉来　家内安全
ウチの寺に
代々　伝わる　おはらいです
This is the purification right from our temple.
これで　もう大丈夫
呪いなんて　心配な～い
You're safe now.
Don't worry about the curse!
Really?
マジで～？　やった～
Yay!
そっかあ　よかった～
Really?
Great!
Easy as pie.
（ニャムサス）うまくいったみたいだね
Looks like it worked.
（タマ）おみそれしやした
That was brilliant, Nee-san.
（ノワール）人間って　単純
People are so simple.
Ambulance coming through!
Beep, beep!
（爺）緊急車両　通ります
（凪）ピーポー　ピーポー　いざ退院
あれ？　あれは後輩達ではないか→
Hey, there are my kouhai.
楽しそうだな　君達
私も　ぜひ　まぜろ
What a coincidence, guys!
Let me join the fun too!
Um, the second season...
あの　２期が…　あッ　ない
いったん　ＣＭ
There isn't one?
Off to commercials.
にゃんこい！　ニャニャ～ン
Nyan Koi! Nya! Nya!
Hey, Kousaka...
おや　高坂？
そのネコ耳…
Are those cat ears?
わあーッ　もう見ないで　バカ～
Don't look, dummy!
ちょッ　高坂くん！？
（ニャムサス）追うよ
Hey! Kousaka-kun!
After him!
（タマ）ガッテン
（ノワール）待ちなさい
Okay!
Wait up!
We'll go too!
私達も
うん
せッ　先輩　今のアレ
S-Senpai, was that...
グッジョブ　さすが高坂
Good job, Kousaka.
なかなかキュ～ンとくる仮装だ
えッ？
That's a very enticing costume.
Crazy.
≪（晴彦）あれ～
ナギー先輩も出るの？
Hey, you're in this too, Nagi-senpai?
（晃太）ワイハへの切符は
いただくぜ
I'll win the trip to Hawaii!
フンフンフンッ　天才ですから～
Because I'm a genius!
な～んだ　知らんのか？
商店街の仮装コンテストだ
Didn't you know about this?
The shopping district is holding a costume contest.
優勝すると
豪華賞品が　もらえるらしい
Apparently, the winners will receive great prizes!
はあ…
そうだ　楓も　ぜひ出るとよい
I have an idea.
You should enter too!
衣装も貸すぞ
たとえば　この猫の着ぐるみなど
I'll let you borrow a costume!
Like this cat costume!
ボツデザインであるのが不思議
I rejected the idea, but it's still good.
Don't make the competition more difficult.
（晴彦）これ以上
倍率　上げないでよ～
Besides, you spent so much money on yours! It's not fair!
大体　おとなげねえっすよ
そんな　金かけて
（凪）甘いな
取れるものは　すべて取る
You're naive.
I'll try to win everything I can.
That is the way of a godfa— no, of a ruler!
それがドン　いや　覇王への道！
おもしれえ　やってみろ！
Fine! Bring it on!
〈でも　さっきのアレ…〉
But weren't those...
すみません　ちょっと行ってきます
I'm sorry, but I'm going to check on him.
あッ…
何事だ？
What's happening?
ただごとではない雰囲気でしたな
うん？
It looks serious.
≪ニャ～ッ
スリラー！
No way!
ウソ！？
これって…
No...
Does this mean...
ああ…
高坂く～ん！
Kousaka-kun!
あッ　ヤッバ
Crap!
ふ～う…　あッ
琴音ちゃん
Kotone-chan!
S-So that's where you were hiding it.
そッ　そんなところに
ダメ　通信不能
あッ→
This is bad.
No transmission detected.
呪いが…　一刻も早く
水野って人の疑いを解かないと
It must be the curse.
We need to clear up Mizuno's
misunderstanding as soon as possible.
急いで　捜しましょう
Let's hurry and find her.
うん
ニャー
Crap, I'm fading out.
クソッ　気が遠くなってきやがった
〈やっぱ　バチが当たったのかな〉
I guess this is payment for my sins.
〈水野を
だまそうとしたりすっから〉
After all, I tried to trick Mizuno.
〈ああ　出た　走馬灯〉
And now my life passes before my eyes.
〈しっかし　ホント
ロクなことしてねえな　俺〉
Anyway, all I've done is give her crap.
Sorry, Mizuno.
〈ごめん　水野
せめて　もういっぺん〉
I wanted to see you once more and apologize.
〈会って　謝りたかった〉
《高坂く～ん》
Kousaka-kun!
ニャヒ～
ニャ～
どこ行っちゃったのかなあ
高坂くん
Where did he go?
Kousaka-kun...
ニャ～
あッ　うん？
あッ　どうしたの　猫ちゃん！？
Wh-What's wrong, kitty?
ニャ～
あッ
《猫ってさ
かわいがるのは　いいんだけど》
It's okay to love cats, but it's not okay to overdo it.
《その…
かまいすぎるのも　ダメなんだ》
ニャ…
おいで
Come here.
ニャア
〈はッ…　逃げない〉
He's not running away.
Exactly like Kousaka-kun said.
高坂くんの言ってたとおりだ
〈ああ
もう　このまま死んでもいいかも〉
I can die now.
ニャ～オ
あッ
わあ～
スゴイ…
Amazing!
This is so great.
〈うれしい　初めて猫ちゃん達と
仲よくできた〉
I'm finally getting along with cats!
わあ～
〈ニャムサス　僕　もう疲れたよ〉
Nyamsus, I'm exhausted.
ありがとう　高坂くん
私　どうかしてた
Thank you, Kousaka-kun.
I was out of my mind.
だって　高坂くん
You cared so much about cats.
あんなに
猫ちゃん達に優しい人だもの
うん！　やっぱり　あるわけないよ
There's no way...
猫地蔵の呪いなんて！
a cat-statue curse could exist.
あッ
ニャー
ウソだろ…　もッ　戻った？
No way...
I-I'm back!
高坂…
K-Kousa—
K-Kousaka-kun!
あッ　高坂くん！
What?!
高坂くん　そのカッコ！？
これは　その　あのね～
Kousaka-kun, why are you...
Well, you know, this is—
高坂潤平～ッ
おおッ　無事だったか
Kousaka Junpei!
You're all right!
何事かと心配したぞ
全裸め
I was worried that something had happened to you.
あッ　あの
皆さん　そのカッコは？
U-Um, guys, why are you dressed like that?
潤平くん　何してんの？
What are you doing, Junpei-kun?
衣装に着替えてんのか？
Are you changing into your costume?
えッ　衣装って？
What costume?
ヘッ　このオトボケさんめ
Are you trying to play dumb?
いよいよ　イブかあ
It's Christmas Eve.
アタシも　潤平のことなんか忘れて
サンタさんに　新たな恋を…
I'll forget about Junpei and ask Santa for a new love.
That's it!
そうそう　いや～　俺も実は
I was planning to enter the contest too.
その大会に　出るつもりでさあ
いろいろ考えたあげく
So I thought about it, and this is how I ended up.
いきつくとこは　最終的に
これなんじゃねえかって
N-Naked?
裸で？
あッ　うん　そうなんだよね
Y-Yeah, that's it.
You're full of crap!
んなわけ　あるかーッ！
S-Sumiyoshi!
すッ　住吉！
気　変わった
I changed my mind.
やっぱ　テメエを
野放しにしとくわけにはいかねえ
I can't leave you loose in the wild.
はッ　はい！？
Wh-What?!
You pervert!
この変態ヤロー！
お仕置きだ　コラーッ
I'll punish you!
痛い　痛いッ
つきあっちゃえばいいのにね
Seriously, they should be dating.
（凪）Ｄカップ～　私もやりたい！
D-cup, let me join too!
（爺）凪様～ッ
何　これ
エヘヘヘ
What the heck is this?
Oh boy.
Hey, it's snowing.
おや　雪だよ
あッ？
（タマ）た～まや～
（ノワール）ホワイトクリスマスね
Great!
It'll be a white Christmas.
〈俺の呪われた１年は
こうやって幕を閉じた〉
This is how my cursed year came to an end.
〈でもって…〉
And now...
ア　ハッピー　ニュー　イヤー
A Happy New Year!
（鈴）あッ　そろそろじゃない？
I think it's about time.
（母）ああ　そうだねえ
You're right.
Junpei, you're late.
潤平兄ちゃん　遅～い
すんませんでした
Sorry about that.
Let me see.
どれどれ？
お父さんからだ
It's from Dad!
「あけましておめでとう
みんな　元気ですか？」→
"Happy New Year.
I hope everyone's doing well.
「父さんも　今年こそは
ウチに帰りたいです」→
And I'm hoping that I get to come home this year.
Also, be careful about the bell.
「それから　鈴に気をつけろ
当たると　痛いぞ」
If you get hit, it's gonna hurt."
〈意味　わからん〉
I totally don't get it.
Honey!
あなた…
お父さん！→
Dad!
もう顔　思い出せない
I can't even remember his name anymore!
Anyway, I need to continue with my deliveries.
じゃあ　俺　配達あっから
〈俺は　何とか
バイトをクビにならずにすんだ〉
I somehow managed to keep my job.
I'm done with my deliveries.
配達　終わりましたけど
次は何を…
What should I do next?
お疲れ～
もう今日は　上がっていいわよ
Good work.
You can call it a day.
えッ　でも…
ウフッ　私からのお年玉
But...
It's a present from me.
約束　あるんでしょ？
ちッ　違いますって～
You have other plans, don't you?
N-No, I don't!
ニョホホホホ～
テレなくていいのに～
Don't be so embarrassed.
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
青春だねえ
He's so young.
≪あけおめ～　あけおめ～
Sorry.
すみません
必ず　バイト代　持ってきますんで
I'll really bring money from my job sometime.
今日のところは　これで何とか…
This is all I could manage today.
〈猫地蔵は
ひとまず　怒りを収めてくれた〉
The cat statue has cooled its anger for now.
〈でも　呪いは解けたわけじゃない
あくまで　小康状態だ〉
But the curse hasn't been lifted yet.
It's only in remission for the moment.
高坂くん　お待たせ
≪（加奈子）潤平　あけおめ～
Kousaka-kun, here we are.
Junpei, happy New Year!
今年も　よろしく
あッ…
Here's to another great year together!
〈父さん　俺　何だか
幸せになれそうな気がします〉
Dad, I think I'm gonna be happy!
〈今年も
潤平と一緒にいられますように〉
I hope I can stay with Junpei again this year.
〈今年こそ　水野と…　水野と！〉
I hope, with Mizuno...
With Mizuno!
〈みんなが
幸せでいられますように〉
I hope everyone stays happy this year.
〈それと…〉
And...
〈高坂くんと
もっと仲よくなれますように〉
I hope I can get closer to Kousaka-kun.
Nee-san! Happy—
ねえさ～ん　あけまして…→
ニャーッ！
What's wrong with you guys?
何だ　オメエら
You both got hit! That's unreal!
２人で当たるとか　マジありえねえ
２人とも　ツイてんじゃねえの？
Maybe you're in luck!
テメエ
かな～
Hey now!
You think so?
ごッ　５０００万円の鈴に！？
Th-The ¥50,000,000 bell!
ヒビが！
えッ！？
It cracked!
What wonderful misfortune at the very start of the year.
新年早々　ステキな不幸ぶり
このバチ当たりめ～
弁償しなさいよ　弁償！
You blasphemer!
You'd better pay for it!
すッ　すみません　って
俺のせいですか～！？　ああーッ
I-I'm sorry!
Wait, it's my fault?!
Wait!
あッ　高バカ
高坂くん！？
Koubaka?
Kousaka-kun?
Hold it!
（ニャムサス）新年早々
どうなることやら
His luck's running against him right from New Year's Day.
（タマ）先が思いやられやすねえ
His future seems grim.
（ノワール）とことん運のない男
He's truly unlucky.
It wasn't me!
俺じゃなーい！
（朱莉）弁償しなさいよ～ッ
Pay up!
〈やっぱり　俺の受難の日々は〉
My days of misfortune have only just begun.
〈まだまだ始まったばかりだ〉
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru anata no sugata
I see you chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu!
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow!
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
Strawberry Tears
Strawberry tears.
Today's Nyan Koma.
Today's Final Nyan Koma
The new term begins today.
今日から新学期かあ…　痛ッ
Isn't that great?
快感だろ？　今期も　よろしくな
Let's be good again this season.
Not this season, but this term!
今期じゃなくて　今学期！
相変わらず　ドンくさいわねえ
You're as klutzy as always.
I'll put a talisman for misfortune on your back.
不幸になるお札　背中に貼りました
よしなさい！
Stop that!
Fight me over Mizuno Kaede!
水野楓を賭けて　勝負だ！
Again?
…て　今さら？
みんな　何やってるの？
遅刻するよ
What are you guys doing?
We'd better not be late.
あッ　水野…
M-Mizuno.
おはよ　高坂くん
Good morning, Kousaka-kun.
あッ　あの
俺　実は水野のこと
U-Um, the truth is, I have...
There you are!
（千鶴）いたいた　潤平く～ん
やっぱ　こうくるよね～
Junpei-kun!
I knew this would happen!
潤平くん　お父さんから　お手紙よ
Junpei-kun, there's a postcard from your father.
ホントに　いたんだ
I really have one?
"Junpei, after all, which girl are you..."
「潤平
それで結局　お前は　どの子を…」
えッ　どの子を？
いや　何でも…
"Which girl" what?
No, it's nothing!
「あと　２期が決まったそうで
おめでとう」
"Also, I heard about the second season. Congratulations.
I want to make an appearance on the show too."
「父さんも　アニメに出たいです」
２期って　アニメって？
What second season?
What show?
親父
そこまで　ぶっちゃけちゃうんだ
He's so frank about everything.
What will happen to the Master's romance?
果たして　ダンナの恋の行方は
父の正体とは
Nyan Koma
And who actually is his father?
それ以前に
２期はあるのか
And more importantly, is there really a second season?!
猫は恩知らずって
言われがちだけど
People say cats show no appreciation, but we do have great memories.
アタシらにも
記憶力はあってね
皆さんへの　ご恩は
決して忘れやせん
We'll never forget all the good deeds you've done for us.
んじゃまた　いつの日か
I hope to see you again someday!